<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Texts>
	
	<Text Name="JournalEntryA">
		
		<Page>It's been a month since my hospital stay and people are still babytalking me like I'm some sort of freak. As if on a hair trigger I'll cut my own throat in front of them if they don't coddle me like a toddler. Even Kit and the guys walk on eggshells whenever they talk to me. Maybe I deserve the humiliation after the stunt I pulled, though. Swallowing a bottle of pills was a stupid thing to do. Still, I can't help but seethe when some turd I barely know comes up to me with the "you're so brave" line. If I were brave, life wouldn't terrify me so much that I'd try to off myself. If I were brave, I'd tell Alessa that I'm the worst brother in the world, and that I'm sorry for being such a burden. But guess what? I'm not brave. I'm actually the biggest coward there is.</Page>
		
		<Page>Alessa called today. I'm feeling a bit better. Showered for the first time in a week, ate something small. I worry all the time that some day she'll get sick of me. That some day the calls will stop. I love you, big sis. Please don't leave me like Mom did.</Page>
	
	</Text>

	<Text Name="JournalEntryB">

		<Page>A classmate noticed the Wyrdsmith shirt I had on and we talked for a bit. The whole time I thought they were just getting in close to spy the scars on my arm. Turns out they just liked the shirt. Their name is Ren, and apparently they live right across the hall from me: dorm 512. They're kind of a huge dork, but it's nice to be spoken to like a person and not some specimen.</Page>

		<Page>Not going to class today. Hungover.</Page>

	</Text>

	<Text Name="JournalEntryC">

		<Page>Ren was under the bridge when I left class for a smoke. We struck up a conversation. I was right: they're a certified dork. But so am I, I guess... it was a nice talk.</Page>

		<Page>Kit and I are putting together a little shindig for the weekend. These meds must be doing their job because I haven't had this much energy in a very long time. I called Alessa to tell her about our plans and she seemed surprised to hear me so upbeat. Shame sis lives on the other side of the globe or I'd have invited her along, even if she is a total drag at parties. Speaking of, I'm totally not expecting Ren to be into this whole thing but I've decided to invite them over anyways. Maybe they'll turn out to be a total party animal, who knows?</Page>

		<Page>Party animal HOW!</Page>

	</Text>

	<Text Name="JournalEntryD">

		<Page>Drank two Benzephrine rods this morning (500 mgs!!!). Life's fucking good. Left a message for Alessa, love love love you sis! Before lunch invited Ren over and we smoked a few bowls and now we're playing Sanguis III on their console. Don't let them see this but they're kind of cute! They have perfect eyebrows and they're always so nice.</Page>

		<Page>I'm still wired from the Benz, so I'll write a little, then lie in bed until exhaustion overtakes me and I fall into a fitful, broken sleep. Today (yesterday?) was fun. Said goodbye to Ren a few hours ago. We've become so extremely close in these past five months. At the risk of sounding stupid, I think I'm falling in love.</Page>

		<Page>(A pastel sketch of a fox seated in an office chair. They are smiling, dark eyes squinting at the viewer. It is a drawing of Ren.)</Page>

	</Text>

	<Text Name="JournalEntryE">

		<Page>I'm over the moon! Ren stayed the night. We kissed and everything about it was perfect.</Page>

		<Page>Ren and I talked over breakfast today about what happened between us three nights ago. I'm gonna give them space to think things over, but its so hard to be apart from them. I feel so empty when I'm not basking in their presence.</Page>

		<Page>We had sex again. This might be a regular thing.</Page>

	</Text>

	<Text Name="JournalEntryF">

		<Page>It's been a year since I last tried to take my own life. Since meeting Ren, living has been easy. I feel better now than I ever have, and the darkness of last year is the furthest thing from my mind. Admittedly, part of me feels ashamed of this happiness. What have I done to deserve it, exactly? Sometimes I find myself worrying that this is all coming to an end.</Page>

		<Page>I've been thinking about Mom a lot. Sometimes I'll imagine her voice. "You think things are good? Just wait. Things always come crashing down. There are never highs without lows."</Page>

		<Page>I visited Mom's grave today for the first time in two years. Spent about an hour idling in the grass before catching the Gold Line home. Hope you enjoyed the visit, Mom. Sorry I didn't talk to you about much other than school. Didn't think you'd be interested in that "queer shit" I get up to.</Page>

	</Text>

	<Text Name="JournalEntryG">

		<Page>Ren and I were laying in bed together the night of graduation when the words came spilling out of me. "I love you." Ren said nothing back. I waited, and so we lay in silence for an eternity. Then we left bed and watched a movie. The entire time I was pleading in my mind for God to kill me.</Page>

		<Page>I asked for a kiss. I said, "Can I kiss you?" Ren obliged, but I could tell it was out of guilt. I won't ask anymore.</Page>

	</Text>

	<Text Name="JournalEntryH">

		<Page>Son of a bitch is taller than me.</Page>

		<Page>Why wouldn't Ren tell me? Kit got drunk and spilled the beans. Seth, the thirty-year-old hipster dipshit from Writing IV. Ren's been dating that fucking son of a bitch for months now and everyone knew but me. Everyone knew but the crazy loser loverboy. Everyone knew but stupid little Turk.</Page>

	</Text>
	
</Texts>