<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Texts>

	<Text Name="TheEdgeOfConsciousness">

		<Title>The Edge of Consciousness</Title>

		<Page>What is this place? Why are you here? A dense fog blankets your thoughts, making it hard to focus on the questions fizzling in your skull. It feels like something, some inexplicable psychic force, is holding you back from connecting the dots. This should distress you immensely. Your current predicament is, after all, the single most terrifying thing you've ever experienced. But the fact that you can't full make sense of it all doesn't alarm you in the slightest.
		
		</Page>

	</Text>

	<Text Name="AddictivePersonality">

		<Title>Addictive Personality</Title>

		<Page>You like taking drugs. You like drinking. Your brain chemistry constantly craves substances. Your first experience with drugs came at age ten, when your father let you have a sip of his wine at a holiday dinner. Your second was when your older brother offered you a hit off some of his weed when you were only twelve. This is the moment you fell in love with getting high. Since then, shuffling your sobriety has become a regular occurence.
		
		Stimulants are your particular favorite; they speed you up, make you feel superhuman. They turn you into a sexual terminator. Speed and Benzephrine are your drugs of choice. You got hooked on amphetamine after getting a script for it at age fourteen. You discovered Benzephrine not long after, using it to bridge the gaps between refills on your prescription. You learned how to abuse the popular nasal decongestant by watching videos online; the "legal high" scene was booming during your early highschool years. Crack open the tube it comes in to get at the medicated cotton inside. Cut that up, mix it with something acidic (lemon juice was your go-to), and drink the resulting concoction. It's like a poor man's MDMA. Your first attempt at having sex was on the Benz, but the vasoconstriction made it impossible to get an erection so you settled for some heavy petting. Awkward!
	
		Drinking is another staple of your lonely existence. You can binge drink with the best of them, and scarcely suffer hangovers the next morning. Your personal favorite drink is straight rum. No ice, no mixers. Just good old, piratey rum. You'll pour full glasses of the stuff for yourself and ride the blissful wave of insobriety into the wee hours of the night. Ren is the only person who's been able to drink you under the table. They used to take shots of straight grain alcohol - one time they even upended a bottle of the stuff and chugged and chugged... That night was nauseous nightmare, and you still blame yourself for how sick Ren got.
	
		Drugs might tickle the little neurons of your gray matter, but are they worth the trouble they cause? After all, you've been put out of commission for days on end following a binge. Maybe you should cut back a little. Or a lot. Or completely. See, you're still young but the consequences of your substance abuse are just around the corner. You can't party hard like this without dire repurcussions, you reckon. As hellbent on self-annihilation as you sometimes are, it's for the best that you put the booze down, spit out that capsule, and check yourself into an inpatient program.</Page>

	</Text>

	<Text Name="Hypersexuality">

		<Title>Hypersexuality</Title>

		<Page>You notice how you can't keep your dick in your pants? You've got the sexual appetite of a tyrannosaurus, and you're not afraid to be open about it. You wear your attraction on your sleeve. You're competent at seduction. You're even okay in the sack, though that wasn't always the case. What is it about sex that satisfies you so? Why not pursue a more wholesome hobby, like gardening, or chess? Because those things don't make you [REDACTED], dumbass!
		
		For you, sex is about more than just getting your rocks off. You've always considered it to be, at its core, an expression of love. Love that you don't have enough of for yourself. You see how that works? You're starved for intimacy. You can't get enough of it. It makes you feel whole.
	
		There's also the drugs and alcohol complicating things. See, maybe if you weren't high off entactogens you'd be able to stave off the urge to bone strangers. Sadly, not-sober-you is remarkably bad at impulse control. Your inhibition, which is already touchy, gets absolutely annihilated by your drugs of choice. And you're high, or drunk, or both, more often than not.
	
		The scene you hang around is also a kicker. You're not the only one looking to "party". Places like clubs and bars, which you frequent regularly, are hotspots for hookups. Putting yourself in those environments exponentially increases the likelihood of a sexual encounter of some kind. Sometimes right away, almost in public. You like it like that. The danger.
	
		Maybe you should be more restrained in your promiscuous ways. You expose yourself to a lot of danger when you're constantly alone with strangers. Not to mention the threat of catching an STI. You could always fill the void with less risky behavior. Maybe you just need an entourage to go clubbing with, some incentive to stick around and not run off chasing some ass. And cut the drug use down, you hear? That shit can't be good for your heart.</Page>

	</Text>

	<Text Name="RensFriendship">

		<Title>Ren's Friendship</Title>

		<Page>For a while now, Ren Larsen has been your favorite person on earth. You yearn to be {i|supernaturally} close to them, both emotionally and physically. While circumstances have seen to it that you'll never realize your true desire for them, maybe you two can just be friends. Just. Friends. The words taste like acid on your tongue, but you don't altogether discard the idea. After all, your friendship with Ren is one of the most important parts of your life. Just because you can't be more doesn't disqualify you from having a fulfilling relationship with them. Quite the opposite, actually. Deep down you know that you two wouldn't have worked out. Attempting to continue your little tryst would only cause unnecessary friction between the two of you.
		
		So you're learning to deal with just being friends. Not best friends, but still important enough to each other that you'll be in touch for years to come. This is a healthy relational exercise for you! Usually your attempts at romance blow up in your face spectacularly; this time, you were able to - at least eventually - come to an amicable understanding. For a while, you resented Ren for not loving you back. Now, you realize that the love is, and always has, been there, just in a different form. A platonic love.</Page>

	</Text>

	<Text Name="BorderlinePersonalityDisorder">

		<Title>Borderline Personality Disorder</Title>
		
		<Page>You were diagnosed with borderline personality disorder when you were nineteen years old. For a while you didn't quite understand what that meant. The disorder is characterized by a maladaptive pattern of thoughts and behavior that may manifest as the following: impulsivity, emotional dysregulation (intense mood swings), suicidal or parasuicidal behavior, unstable relationships, frantic efforts to avoid abandonment, and identity disturbance. Makes sense, right? It's like reading a summary of the forces that drive your entire existence.

			Impulsivity? You've got that in spades. You're married to your impulses - wed in a back alley ceremony after a drunken night of bad sex. You're a speed freak who will dose, and redose, without a moment's thought. You act purely on emotion. Go with the flow, follow your heart... and your electrochemical cravings.

			Emotional dysregulation, that's fancy talk for being out of control. Yes, you fly into red rages sometimes. You'll be crying crocodile tears one moment, right-as-rain the next. It's especially bad if you haven't slept.

			Suicide is the guillotine you've been strapped to since you were ten years old. You're always itching to pull that lever, to shuffle this mortal coil. Life's painful, and as much as it causes you shame, it feels damn good to know you've got a finger on the escape key.

			Unstable relationships? Been there, done that. It's hard to keep 'em close when you're fluctuating between unrealistic adoration and seething resentment. Your wild emotions are a challenge, to put it lightly. You're at once passionate and intimate, unstable and jealous, paranoid and fearful. Seductive at first, but once you've suckered them in, they can't tolerate the instability.

			Fear. It dominates your relationships. You're terrified of being abandoned by the ones you love. Your constant anticipation of betrayal causes you to judge others harshly, for both perceived and actual issues. This makes for a self-fulfilling prophecy; you're so scared of losing people that you inadvertently push them away. And when they do leave, it crushes you.

			Your self-esteem is highly dependent on the way others treat you, and there are few pains greater than being left behind. Identity disturbance: the inability to form a stable and healthy self-image. Who is Christopher Turkinopoulos? You've never quite figured that out. Some days, he's the unhinged party animal. Others, he's the suave romantic, or the antisocial hermit, or the tortured creative. You can never piece the puzzle together. The pieces just don't fit.

			Maybe "Turk" is just... borderline. Or maybe you're greater than the sum of your personality traits. Whatever the case may be, you struggle to bring order into your life. Oh, how you desperately wish you could just... keep it together! After years of suffering, the realization has dawned on you that you need help. You can't keep this up. You're waging war on your body and your mind with the drugs, the alcohol. The suicidal gestures will get you killed someday. You can't afford to keep losing friendships. Something's gotta be done about this, and fast.</Page>
		
	</Text>

</Texts>