<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<DialogueNodes>

	<!-- 0 -->
	
	<DialogueNode Name="EyeballTv0_0" Speaker="PsycheMonologue" OneShot="True">
		<Text>An enormous, wet eyeball stares out into empty space from atop a tripod. Its pupil dilates and contracts sporadically. Suddenly, it whirls to fixate its gaze on... you. The pupil's contractions cease, and the void within beckons to you.</Text>
		<Response GoToNode="EyeballTv0_0R1A">What..?</Response>
		<Response GoToNode="EyeballTv0_1">(Stare into it.)</Response>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode Name="EyeballTv0_0R1A" Speaker="PsycheMonologue" GoToNode="EyeballTv0_0R1B">
		<Text>Throbbing red veins fringe the milky orb. The iris shimmers with moisture, the ridges of its musculature clearly visible.</Text>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode Name="EyeballTv0_0R1B" Speaker="PsycheMonologue" GoToNode="EyeballTv0_1">
		<Text>Your vision swirls around the eyeball as if being flushed inwards, towards the gaping pupil. You feel an overpowering urge to stare into its darkness...</Text>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode Name="EyeballTv0_1" Speaker="PsycheMonologue" GoToNode="EyeballTv0_2">
		<Text>You cannot resist the compulsion to meet the thing's gaze. You peer into the void and fixate on the blackness. After a few moments, you see...</Text>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode Name="EyeballTv0_2" Speaker="PsycheMonologue">
		<Text>...Nothing. Nothing but emptiness dwells within the thing's dark pupil. You frown with disappointment, and the urge to stare melts from your mind.</Text>
	</DialogueNode>
	
	<!-- 1 -->

	<DialogueNode Name="EyeballTv1_0" Speaker="PsycheMonologue" OneShot="True">
		<Text>You deliver a swift kick to the eyeball as its gaze turns to you. Its glossy surface begins to swell with blood at the site of its injury. That'll show it for messing with you.</Text>
	</DialogueNode>

	<!-- 2 -->

	<DialogueNode Name="EyeballTv2_0" Speaker="PsycheMonologue" OneShot="True">
		<Text>The eyeball averts its gaze from you. The pupil dilates wide, and droplets of moisture bead on its surface. Is it... afraid?</Text>
	</DialogueNode>
	
</DialogueNodes>