<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<DialogueNodes>

	<DialogueNode Name="RenBossIntro0" Speaker="PsycheMonologue">
		<Text>Perched atop an outcropping of bone stands the broad-shouldered figure of Ren Larsen. They clutch a rifle close to their chest.</Text>
		<Response GoToNode="RenBossIntro0R1A">Ren...</Response>
		<Response GoToNode="RenBossIntro0R1A">I missed you so much.</Response>
		<Response GoToNode="RenBossIntro0R1A">You've got some explaining to do!</Response>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode Name="RenBossIntro0R1A" Speaker="PsycheMonologue" GoToNode="RenBossIntro0R1B">
		<Text>Ren regards you with a scrutinizing stare. Through squinted eyes, they scan over every inch of you. Their gaze feels uncomfortable on your body, and you reflexively shrink away from the dirty look.</Text>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode Name="RenBossIntro0R1B" Speaker="PsycheMonologue" GoToNode="RenBossIntro1">
		<Text>Something isn't right. Ren's eyeballing you like a piece of meat, and not in a good way.</Text>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode Name="RenBossIntro1" Speaker="RenBossGrinning">
		<Text>Their maw suddenly splits into a malicious fanged grin. "Come to lay yourself at my feet? Beg for me back? Grovel for pussy, like the worm you are?" This is not Ren. You can tell by the way it speaks, in a stilted facsimile of Ren's voice. Whatever it is has embers of hatred glowing in the pit of its dark eyes.</Text>
		<Response GoToNode="RenBossIntro1R1A">I'll do anything to have you back.</Response>
		<Response GoToNode="RenBossIntro1R2A">After what you pulled? How dare you!</Response>
		<Response GoToNode="RenBossIntro2">Ren, why would you say that?</Response>
		<Response GoToNode="RenBossIntro1R4A">You'll be the one begging... for this dick!</Response>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode Name="RenBossIntro1R1A" Speaker="RenBossGrinning" GoToNode="RenBossIntro2">
		<Text>The apparition of Ren explodes into laughter. "You really are a worm. An insignificant little insect."</Text>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode Name="RenBossIntro1R2A" Speaker="RenBossGrinning" GoToNode="RenBossIntro2">
		<Text>"I discarded you like the trash you are. Worthless." They swat the air with their hand in a gesture of disgust.</Text>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode Name="RenBossIntro1R4A" Speaker="RenBossGrinning" GoToNode="RenBossDick1">
		<Text>"Disgusting little..." The apparition snaps it salivating jaws. "I'll rip your tiny little cock right off and force-feed it to you!"</Text>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode Name="RenBossDick1" Speaker="PsycheLibido">
		<Text>Yes. Show them your dick. They can't resist you. It'll be just like old times... it's been so damn long since you were last...</Text>
		<Response GoToNode="RenBossDick1R1A">Don't pretend you don't still want me!</Response>
		<Response GoToNode="RenBossDick1R2A">I'm desperate. Please.</Response>
		<Response GoToNode="RenBossDick1R3A">That was a bad joke, I'll admit...</Response>
		<Response GoToNode="RenBossDick1R4A">(Display your dick.)</Response>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode Name="RenBossDick1R1A" Speaker="RenBossGrinning" GoToNode="RenBossDick2">
		<Text>"Ha! I never wanted you. I settled for you. I debased myself by letting you into my bed, you cretin." The apparition spits in your direction.</Text>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode Name="RenBossDick1R2A" Speaker="RenBossGrinning" GoToNode="RenBossDick2">
		<Text>Another hideous laugh, halfway between a bark and a shriek. "I'm going to enjoy putting you out of your misery. Wretch. Puny little..."</Text>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode Name="RenBossDick1R3A" Speaker="RenBossGrinning" GoToNode="RenBossDick2">
		<Text>"I see through your pathetic ruse. You want to fuck me. If this is your best attempt, I was right about you. Disgusting filth. Filth!"</Text>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode Name="RenBossDick1R4A" Speaker="RenBossGrinning" GoToNode="RenBossDickNasty">
		<Text>Not-Ren howls with laughter at the sight of your erection. "You think that inchworm will impress me? You're even sadder than I thought."</Text>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode Name="RenBossDickNasty" Speaker="PsycheLibido">
		<Text>Put on a show for them. Remind them what it was like. This is all a game, and you're playing to win.</Text>
		<Response GoToNode="RenBossDickNastyR1A">(Begin masturbating.)</Response>
		<Response GoToNode="RenBossDick2">(Put your junk away.)</Response>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode Name="RenBossDickNastyR1A" Speaker="RenBossGrinning" GoToNode="RenBossShootsYourDick">
		<Text>Without a moment's hesitation, Not-Ren swings its rifle into firing position - aimed directly at your pecker.</Text>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode Name="RenBossDick2" Speaker="RenBossGrinning" GoToNode="RenBossDick3">
		<Text>"Your perverted little kiddie-fantasy of getting with me? It's gonna die screaming." The beast levels its weapon at your crotch.</Text>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode Name="RenBossDick3" Speaker="PsycheDiscipline">
		<Text>What the fuck are you doing? You're going to get yourself killed. Move, quickly, you're about to get shot!</Text>
		<Response GoToNode="RenBossShootsYourDick">You wouldn't hurt me.</Response>
		<Response GoToNode="RenBossShootsYourDickMiss">(Dive for cover.)</Response>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode Name="RenBossShootsYourDickMiss" Speaker="PsycheMonologue" GoToNode="RenBossDick3">
		<Text>You quickly leap to one side, throwing yourself like a ragdoll to the hard ground beneath you. There's a sharp crack as the rifle discharges. You feel the shockwave - but no pain. The shot struck the ground about a foot away from you.</Text>
	</DialogueNode>

	<DialogueNode Name="RenBossIntro2" Speaker="RenBossGrinning">
		<Text>Not-Ren licks its lips with a dripping, red tongue. "Can't you take a hint?! You weren't shit to me. As soon as I could trade you in for someone better, I did!" </Text>
		<Response GoToNode="RenBossIntro2R1A">I know, and I'll never forgive you.</Response>
		<Response GoToNode="RenBossIntro2R2A">I always knew you felt that way.</Response>
		<Response GoToNode="RenBossIntro2R3A">That's... that's not you, is it?</Response>
		<Response GoToNode="RenBossIntro2R4A">You're a projection. A twisted lie.</Response>
	</DialogueNode>

</DialogueNodes>